<resources>
    <!-- Title for the application. [CHAR LIMIT=12] -->
    <string name="app_name">Tour Kolkata</string>

    <!-- Category name for heritage spots [CHAR LIMIT=20] -->
    <string name="category_heritage">Heritage</string>

    <!-- Category name for religious spots [CHAR LIMIT=20] -->
    <string name="category_religious">Religious</string>

    <!-- Category name for nature spots [CHAR LIMIT=20] -->
    <string name="category_nature">Nature</string>

    <!-- Category name for sports spots [CHAR LIMIT=20] -->
    <string name="category_sports">Sports</string>

    <!-- Category name for other spots [CHAR LIMIT=20] -->
    <string name="category_others">Others</string>

    <!-- Description of the tourist spots in Heritage category -->
    <string name="victoria_memorial">The Victoria Memorial is a large marble building in Kolkata,
        West Bengal, India, which was built between 1906 and 1921. It is dedicated to the memory of
        Queen Victoria, then Empress of India, and is now a museum under the auspices of the
        Ministry of Culture. The memorial lies on the Maidan, near Jawaharlal Nehru Road
        (also known as Chowringhee Road).</string>

    <string name="fort_william">Fort William is a fort in Hastings, Calcutta (Kolkata). It was built
        during the early years of the Bengal Presidency of British India. It sits on the eastern
        banks of the Hooghly River, the major distributary of the River Ganges. One of Kolkata\'s
        most enduring Raj-era edifices, it extends over an area of 70.9 hectares. The fort was named
        after King William III. In front of the Fort is the Maidan, the largest park in the city.
        An internal guard room became the Black Hole of Calcutta.</string>

    <string name="howrah_bridge">Howrah Bridge is a balanced cantilever bridge over the Hooghly
        River in West Bengal, India. Commissioned in 1943, the bridge was originally named the New
        Howrah Bridge, because it replaced a pontoon bridge at the same location linking the two
        cities of Howrah and Kolkata (Calcutta). On 14 June 1965 it was renamed Rabindra Setu after
        the great Bengali poet Rabindranath Tagore, who was the first Indian and Asian Nobel
        laureate. It is still popularly known as the Howrah Bridge. The bridge is one of four on the
        Hooghly River and is a famous symbol of Kolkata and West Bengal. The other bridges are the
        Vidyasagar Setu (popularly called the Second Hooghly Bridge), the Vivekananda Setu and the
        newly built Nivedita Setu. It weathers the storms of the Bay of Bengal region, carrying a
        daily traffic of approximately 100,000 vehicles and possibly more than 150,000 pedestrians,
         easily making it the busiest cantilever bridge in the world. The third-longest cantilever
        bridge at the time of its construction, the Howrah Bridge is currently the sixth-longest
        bridge of its type in the world.</string>

    <string name="indian_museum">The Indian Museum in Kolkata, West Bengal, India, also referred to
        as the Imperial Museum at Calcutta in colonial-era texts, is the ninth oldest museum in the
        world, the oldest museum in India, and the largest museum in India. It has rare collections
        of antiques, armour and ornaments, fossils, skeletons, mummies and Mughal paintings. It was
        founded by the Asiatic Society of Bengal in Kolkata (Calcutta), India, in 1814. The founder
        curator was Nathaniel Wallich, a Danish botanist. It has six sections comprising thirty five
        galleries of cultural and scientific artifacts namely Indian art, archaeology, anthropology,
        geology, zoology and economic botany. Many rare and unique specimens, both Indian and
        trans-Indian, relating to humanities and natural sciences, are preserved and displayed in
        the galleries of these sections. In particular the art and archaeology sections hold
        collections of international importance. It is an autonomous organization under Ministry of
        Culture, Government of India. The present Director of the Indian Museum is Shri Arijit Dutta
        Choudhury who is also the Director General, NCSM and having the additional charge of
        Director General of National Library. Administrative control of the Cultural sections, viz.
        Art, Archaeology and Anthropology rests with the Board of Trustees under its Directorate,
        and that of the three other science sections is with the geological survey of India, the
        zoological survey of India and the Botanical survey of India. The museum Directorate has
        eight co-ordinating service units: Education, preservation, publication, presentation,
        photography, medical, modelling and library. This multipurpose institution with
        multidisciplinary activities is being included as an Institute of national importance in the
        seventh schedule of the Constitution of India.</string>

    <string name="marble_palace">Marble Palace is a palatial nineteenth-century mansion in North
        Kolkata. It is located at 46, Muktaram Babu Street, Kolkata 700007. It is one of the
        best-preserved and most elegant houses of nineteenth-century Calcutta. The mansion is famous
        for its marble walls, floors, and sculptures, from which it derives its name.</string>

    <string name="mother_house">The Missionaries of Charity’s Mother House is a holy place of
        pilgrimage and reverence for those who are searching for a more meaningful existence. It was
        established by the Blessed Mother Teresa in 1950 with the purpose of selfless service to
        mankind and to uplift the plagued humanity towards the path of salvation. After Mother
        Teresa left her mortal body in 1997, she was laid to rest in a tomb inside the house where
        she lived and served. The site of the tomb is very simple yet it exudes enormous amount of
        benign and pure vibration that fills the heart with gratitude and peace. Situated amidst
        noise and crowd, Mothers tomb is a true reflection of her life which contemplated the
        example of soulful and mindful meditation. he Mother House- Missionaries of Charity is
        situated near Ripon Street. Its nearest landmark is the Sealdah Loreto Convent.</string>

    <string name="jorasanko_thakurbari">Jorasanko Thakur Bari (Bengali: House of the Thakurs
        (anglicised to Tagore) in Jorasanko, North Kolkata, West Bengal, India, is the ancestral
        home of the Tagore family. It is currently located on the Rabindra Bharati University
        campus at 6/4 Dwarakanath Tagore Lane, Jorasanko, Kolkata 700007. It is the house in which
        the poet and first non-European Nobel laureate, Rabindranath Tagore was born. It is also
        the place where he spent most of his childhood and died on 7 August 1941</string>

    <string name="shobhabajar_rajbari">Shobhabazar Rajbari (Shobhabazar Royal Palace) is the palace
        of the Shobhabazar royal family located in the Indian city of Kolkata. Maharaja Nabakrishna
        Deb (1737–97), founder of the Shobhabazar Rajbari (at 35), started life as a modest
        aristocrat but soon amassed considerable wealth in his service to the British, in particular
        by his role in assisting to topple Siraj ud-Daulah. During his lifetime Raja Nabakrishna Deb
        built two houses. The building at 35 Raja Nabakrishna Street (known as Shobhabazar Rajbari
        or "Baag ola Bari - House with the lions"), on the northern side of the road, was the one
        first constructed by him, subsequently inherited by his adopted son from his elder brother
        Gopimohan and his descendants including his son Radhakanta Deb. The house at 33 Raja
        Nabakrishna Street (known as Choto Rajbari) was built by him when a son was born to him
        later in life, and was left to his biological son Rajkrishna and his descendants.</string>

    <string name="prinsep_ghat">Prinsep Ghat is a ghat built in 1841 during the British Raj, along
        the Kolkata bank of the Hooghly River in India. The Palladian porch in the memory of the
        eminent Anglo-Indian scholar and antiquary James Prinsep was designed by W. Fitzgerald and
        constructed in 1843. Located between the Water Gate and the St George\'s Gate of the Fort
        William, the monument to Prinsep is rich in Greek and Gothic inlays. It was restored by the
        state\'s public works department in November 2001 and has since been well-maintained. In its
        initial years, all royal British entourages used the Prinsep Ghat jetty for embarkation and
        disembarkation.</string>

    <string name="national_library">The National Library of India is the largest library located in
        Belvedere Estate, Alipore, Kolkata, India. It is India\'s largest library by volume and
        public record. National Library is under the Ministry of Culture, Government of
        India. The library is designated to collect, disseminate and preserve printed material
        produced in India. It is the largest in India with a collection in excess of 2.2 million
        books. Before independence, it was the official residence of Governor-General of India. The
        library operates under the national government’s Department of Culture and is designated to
        collect, disseminate, and preserve all printed material produced in India. The National
        Library is a result of the merging of the public library with the Imperial Library—several
        government libraries. The National Library (1953), then the Imperial Library housed several
        foreign (British) and Indian titles and was open to the public. It collects book,
        periodicals, and titles in virtually all the Indian languages while the special collections
        in the National Library of India house at least fifteen languages. The Hindi department
        has books that date back all the way to the nineteenth century and the first ever books
        printed in that language. The collections break down and consist of 86,000 maps and 3,200
        manuscripts.</string>

    <string name="shaheed_minar">The Shaheed Minar (English: Martyrs\' Monument), formerly known as
        the Ochterlony Monument, is a monument in Kolkata that was erected in 1828 in memory of
        Major-general Sir David Ochterlony, commander of the British East India Company, to
        commemorate both his successful defense of Delhi against the Marathas in 1804 and the
        victory of the East India Company’s armed forces over the Gurkhas in the Anglo-Nepalese War
        also known as the Gurkha War. The monument was constructed in his memory. It was designed by
        J. P. Parker and paid for from public funds. On 9 August 1969 it was rededicated to the
        memory of the martyrs of the Indian freedom movement and renamed the "Shaheed Minar," which
        means "martyrs' monument" in both Bengali and Hindi, by the then United Front Government in
        memory of the martyrs of the Indian independence movement. The present
        [when?] government has decided to illuminate the tower during evenings and allow visitors to
        the top. The last people to have been up there were former governor Gopal Krishna
        Gandhi and his family.</string>

    <string name="raj_bhavan">Raj Bhavan is the official residence of the Governor of West Bengal,
        located in the capital city Kolkata. Built in 1803, it was known as Government House before
        the independence of India. After the transfer of power from the East India Company to the
        British Crown in 1858, it became the official residence of the Viceroy of India, shifting
        here from the Belvedere Estate. With the shifting of capital to Delhi in 1911 it became the
        official residence of Lieutenant Governor of Bengal. Since independence in 1947 it serves as
        the official residence of the Governor of West Bengal and came to be known as the Raj
        Bhavan, a name it shares with the official residences of other states\' governors.</string>

    <string name="netaji_bhavan">Netaji Bhawan or Netaji Bhavan (Netaji\'s Residence) is a building
        maintained as a memorial and research center to the life of the Indian nationalist "Netaji"
        Subhas Chandra Bose in Kolkata. The house, built by Bose\'s father in 1909, is owned
        and managed by the Netaji Research Bureau and includes a museum, archives and library.
        The Bureau is run by Sugata Bose and his mother, Krishna Bose(at February 2020 expired). The
        building is on Lala Lajpat Rai Sarani in Kolkata.</string>

    <!-- Description of the tourist spots in Religious category -->
    <string name="belur_math">Beluṛ Maṭh is the headquarters of the Ramakrishna Math and Mission,
        founded by Swami Vivekananda, the chief disciple of Ramakrishna Paramahamsa. It is located
        on the west bank of Hooghly River, Belur, West Bengal, India and is one of the significant
        institutions in Kolkata. This temple is the heart of the Ramakrishna Movement. The temple is
        notable for its architecture that fuses Christian, Islamic, Hindu and Buddhist art motifs as
        a symbol of unity of all religions. In 2003 Belur Math railway station was also inaugurated
        which is dedicated to Belur Math Temple.</string>
    <string name="dakshineswar">Dakshineswar Kali Temple is a Hindu navaratna temple located at
        Dakshineswar. Situated on the eastern bank of the Hooghly River, the presiding deity of the
        temple is Bhavatarini, an aspect of Kali, who is form of Adi Shakti. The temple was built in
        1855 by Rani Rashmoni, a philanthropist and a devotee of Kali. The temple is known for its
        association with Ramakrishna and Ma Sarada Devi, mystics of 19th Century Bengal. The temple
        compound, apart from the nine-spired main temple, contains a large courtyard surrounding the
        temple, with rooms along the boundary walls. There are twelve shrines dedicated to
        Shiva—Kali\'s companion—along the riverfront, a temple to Radha-Krishna, a bathing ghat on
        the river, a shrine dedicated to Rani Rashmoni. \'Nahabat\', the chamber in the northwestern
        corner just beyond the last of the Shiva temples, is where Ramakrishna and Maa Sarada spent
        a considerable part of their lives.</string>
    <string name="st_pauls_cathedral">St. Paul\'s Cathedral is a Church of North India (CNI)
        cathedral of Anglican background in Kolkata, West Bengal, India, noted for its Gothic
        architecture and dedicated to Paul the Apostle. It is the seat of the Diocese of Calcutta.
        The cornerstone was laid in 1839; the building was completed in 1847. It is said to be the
        largest church in Kolkata and the first Anglican cathedral in Asia. It was also the first
        new-built cathedral in the overseas territory of the British Empire. The edifice stands on
        Cathedral Road on the "island of attractions" to provide for more space for the growing
        population of the European community in Calcutta in the 1800s. The architectural design of
        the cathedral is \"Indo-Gothic\", a Gothic architectural style designed to meet the climate
        of India. Following the 1897 earthquake and the subsequent massive earthquake of 1934, when
        Calcutta suffered substantial damage, the cathedral was reconstructed to a revised design.
        The cathedral complex has a library, situated over the western porch, and a display of
        plastic art forms and memorabilia. Apart from that of Bishop Daniel Wilson, the founder of
        the cathedral, the other notable burial in the church is that of John Paxton Norman, an
        acting Chief Justice who was assassinated on the steps of Kolkata Town Hall in 1871.</string>
    <string name="birla_mandir">Birla Mandir in Kolkata, India, is a Hindu temple on Asutosh
        Chowdhury Avenue, Ballygunge, built by the industrialist Birla family. This temple is open
        in the morning from 5.30 A.M. to 11 A.M. and in the evening from 4 .30 P.M. to 9 P.M. On
        Janmashtami, the birthday of Krishna, devotees come from far away places to pay their
        respect to the deities.</string>
    <string name="kalighat_temple">Kalighat Kali Temple is a Hindu temple in Kalighat, Kolkata,
        West Bengal, India dedicated to the Hindu goddess Kali. It is one of the 51 Shakti Peethas.
        Kalighat was a Ghat (landing stage) sacred to Kali on the old course (Adi Ganga) of the
        Hooghly river (Bhāgirathi) in the city of Kolkata. The name Calcutta is said to have been
        derived from the word Kalighat. The river over a period of time has moved away from the
        temple. The temple is now on the banks of a small canal called Adi Ganga which connects to
        the Hooghly. The Adi Ganga was the original course of the river Hooghly. Hence the name Adi
        (original) Ganga.</string>
    <string name="nakhoda_masjid">The Nakhoda Masjid is the principal mosque of Kolkata, India, in
        the Chitpur area of the Burrabazar business district in Central Kolkata, at the intersection
        of Zakaria Street and Rabindra Sarani.</string>
    <string name="jain_temple">Calcutta Jain Temple (also called Parshwanath Temple) is a Jain
        temple at Badridas Temple Street, Gouribari in Maniktala and a major tourist attraction of
        Kolkata (Calcutta), India. The temple was built by a Jain named Rai Badridas Bahadoor Mookim
        in 1867. Pratishtha was done by Sri Kalyansurishwarji Maharaj.</string>
    <string name="south_park_street_cemetery">South Park Street Cemetery is located on Mother Teresa
        Sarani, Kolkata, India. The road used to be called Park Street, and prior to that Burial
        Ground Road.</string>
    <string name="buddhist_pagoda">The Buddhist Pagoda is more than a 150 year old architecture that
        was brought from Burma itself. The pagoda has its typical architecture which looks out of
        place in the city of joy, standing serenly behind the more famous Eden garden stadium. It
        attracts a few buddhist locals and some wandering tourists in the are.</string>
    <string name="st_james_church">St. James\' Church in Entally, Kolkata (Calcutta), India, is one
        of Kolkata\'s most elegant churches. Built in 1862, the twin spires of the St. James\'
        Church dominates Kolkata\'s skyline. It is popularly known as Jora Girja, literally meaning
        twin church for its twin spires.</string>
    <string name="st_johns_church">St. John\'s Church, originally a cathedral, was among the first
        public buildings erected by the East India Company after Kolkata (Calcutta) became the
        effective capital of British India. It is located at the North-Western corner of Raj Bhavan,
        and served as the Anglican Cathedral of Calcutta till 1847, when the see was transferred to
        St. Paul\'s Cathedral. Construction of the building, modelled on St Martin-in-the-Fields of
        London, started in 1784, with Rs 30,000 raised through a public lottery, and was completed
        in 1787. The land the church stands on was gifted by Maharaja Nabo Kishen Bahadur of
        Sobhabazar. It is the third oldest church in the city, next to the Armenian Church of the
        Holy Nazareth and the Old Mission Church</string>

    <!-- Description of the tourist spots in Nature category -->
    <string name="rabindra_sarovar">Rabindra Sarobar (previously known as Dhakuria Lake) is an
        artificial lake in South Kolkata in the Indian state of West Bengal. The name also refers to
        the area surrounding the lake. It is flanked by Southern Avenue to the North, Shyamaprasad
        Mukherjee Road to the West, Dhakuria to the East and the Kolkata Suburban Railway tracks to
        the south.</string>
    <string name="botanical_gardens">The Acharya Jagadish Chandra Bose Indian Botanic Garden
        previously known as Indian Botanic Garden and the Calcutta Botanic Garden, is situated in
        Shibpur, Howrah near Kolkata. They are commonly known as the Calcutta Botanical Garden and
        previously as the Royal Botanic Garden, Calcutta. The gardens exhibit a wide variety of
        rare plants and a total collection of over 12,000 specimens spread over 109 hectares. It is
        under Botanical Survey of India (BSI) of Ministry of Environment and Forests, Government of
        India.</string>
    <string name="alipore_zoo">The Zoological Garden, Alipore (also informally called the Alipore
        Zoo or Calcutta Zoo) is India\'s oldest formally stated zoological park (as opposed to royal
        and British menageries) and a big tourist attraction in Kolkata, West Bengal. It has been
        open as a zoo since 1876, and covers 18.811 ha (46.48 acres). It is probably best known as
        the home of the now expired Aldabra giant tortoise Adwaita, who was reputed to have been
        over 250 years old when he died in 2006. It is also home to one of the few captive breeding
        projects involving the Manipur brow-antlered deer. One of the most popular tourist
        attractions in Kolkata, it draws huge crowds during the winter season, especially during
        December and January. The highest attendance till date was on January 1, 2018 with 110,000
        visitors.</string>
    <string name="eco_tourism_park">Eco Park (Prakriti Tirtha) is an urban park in New Town,
        Rajarhat, Kolkata and the biggest park so far in India. The park is situated on a 480 acres
        (190 ha) plot and is surrounded by a 104 acres (42 ha) waterbody with an island in the
        middle. The park was conceptualised by Chief Minister of West Bengal, Mamata Banerjee in
        July 2011. West Bengal Housing Infrastructure Development Corporation (HIDCO) is the
        overarching body coordinating the construction of the park, along with different other
        government bodies responsible for implementation of different works inside the park. The
        park has been divided into three broad parts; 1) ecological zones like wetlands, grasslands,
        and urban forest, 2) theme gardens and open spaces, 3) and urban recreational spaces. The
        Eco Park is further divided into different sub-parts according to the different types of
        fauna planted. The copies of the Seven Wonders of the World have also been made for people
        to visit in this park. According to the plan, the park will have different areas like wild
        flower meadows, a bamboo garden, grasslands, tropical tree garden, bonsai garden,
        tea garden, Cactus Walk, a heliconia garden, a butterfly garden, a play area and an
        amphitheatre. Further, there is plan to develop an eco-resort in public-private partnership,
        and will also include an area where handicrafts from different part of the state will be
        exhibited. The park was inaugurated on 29 December 2012 by Mamata Banerjee.</string>
    <string name="maidan">The Maidan (literally, open field), also referred to as the Brigade Parade
        Ground, is the largest urban park in Kolkata in the Indian state of West Bengal. It is a
        vast stretch of field that includes numerous play grounds, including the famous cricketing
        venue Eden Gardens, several football stadiums and the Kolkata Race Course. The Maidan is
        dotted with statues and architectural works, the most notable being the Victoria Memorial.
        Due to the freshness and greenery it provides to the metropolis, it has been referred to as
        the \"lungs of Kolkata\". The property of the Indian Army, the Maidan hosts the army\'s Eastern
        zone high command in Fort William. The Maidan stretches from the Raj Bhavan building on the
        Esplanade in the north to the National Library on Belvedere Road in Alipore in the south.
        The wide field stretches from the Hooghly River in the west to the Victoria Memorial in the
        east. It is a historical and cultural center of Kolkata as well as a center of leisure and
        entertainment for Calcuttans.</string>
    <string name="central_park">Central Park situated in Salt Lake is a public urban park. It is
        also known as Banabitan. It is the second largest open space in Kolkata Metropolitan Area
        after the Maidan. It is a favorite hangout for lovers. This park is easily reachable from
        the Karunamoyee Bus Terminus in Salt Lake. Central Park metro station and depot of Kolkata
        Metro Line 2 are located here. On the roads surrounding the park are the buildings where the
        West Bengal government has relocated many government departments. The park is built around
        an expansive water body. There is a bridge which connects on side of the lake to an island
        which has a pagoda. The lake serves as a haven for water birds like lesser whistling duck,
        common moorhen, egrets, cormorants and other species. There are also boating facilities in a
        cordoned off section of the lake near the rose garden.</string>
    <string name="millenium_park">Millennium Park is a private park in Kolkata, situated along the
        Strand Road on eastern shore of Hooghly River for a stretch of 2.5 km near Fairlie Ghat and
        opposite to Railway Club. The park consists of landscaped gardens and children\'s amusement
        rides. It was opened along the riverside to provide a green area for Kolkata\'s polluted
        waterway. It is a millennium gift from Kolkata Metropolitan Development Authority
        (KMDA/CMDA) inaugurated on 26 December 1999. The park is part of the first phases of the
        Kolkata Riverside Beautification Project. The park is open from 11am-8pm.</string>
    <string name="nalban">The unique thing about this boating complex is the lake that measures
        nearly 400 acres in surface area. Emerald green waters, surrounding plantations, calmness
        and the seclusion coalesce to make this place utterly romantic! Both locals and tourists
        from places near and far visit this place to enjoy picnics. Although there are many things
        to do here, the most popular of all activities is boating. Paddle boats, shikaras,
        hovercrafts or rowing boats – choose what you like most among these and set off for a joyful
        ride across the waters. Feel the cool breeze of the lake kissing your skin and get
        mesmerised! At Nalban Boating Complex, there is a well-decorated food joint where you can
        step in to relish mouth-watering Indian and international delicacies, in addition to a wide
        variety of refreshing beverages. The complex also serves as an ideal place for events like
        private parties, marriages and anniversaries.</string>
    <string name="subhash_sarovar">The grandiose Subhash Sarovar is a wonderful place for day
        outings and family picnics. This lake adds to the natural beauty of this area, one can have
        a close look through boating on the Lake. Morning walks around the shore of this lake is a
        perfect way to start your mornings. The place is also a paradise for birdwatchers and
        photographers alike.</string>
    <string name="hoogly_riverfront">Hooghly Riverfront is composed of the two banks of the Hooghly
        River, which runs between the city of Kolkata on the east and the city of Howrah on the west
        in West Bengal, India. On the east bank of the river, a beautification started in 2011, of
        which the first phase ended in 2012.</string>

    <!-- Description of the tourist spots in sports category -->
    <string name="eden_gardens">The Eden Gardens is a cricket ground in Kolkata, India. Established
        in 1864, it is the oldest and second largest cricket stadium in India after the newly built
        Sardar Patel Stadium and third in the world after Sardar Patel Stadium and Melbourne Cricket
        Ground. The stadium currently has a capacity of 80,000. On 22 November 2019, the venue
        hosted the first ever day/night test match in India during second Test between India and
        Bangladesh. Eden Gardens is often referred to as home of Indian cricket. It has the fastest
        outfield among all the cricket stadiums in India therefore it is regarded as \"Batsman\'s
        Paradise\".The ground has been referred to as \"cricket\'s answer to the Colosseum\". Eden
        Gardens is called the \“Mecca of Indian cricket\” because it was the first officially built
        ground for the game of cricket in India. Eden Gardens has hosted matches in major
        international competitions including the World Cup, World Twenty20 and Asia Cup. In 1987,
        Eden Gardens became the second stadium to host a World Cup final. The 2016 ICC World
        Twenty20 final was held at the Eden Gardens where the West Indies beat England in a very
        closely fought encounter.</string>
    <string name="salt_lake_stadium">The Salt Lake Stadium, officially the Vivekananda Yuba Bharati
        Krirangan (VYBK; transl. Vivekananda Indian Youth Stadium), is a multipurpose stadium in
        Bidhannagar, Kolkata, with a current capacity of 85,000. The Salt Lake Stadium is the main
        home of ATK Mohun Bagan, East Bengal. It is the second largest stadium in India by seating
        capacity. Before its renovation in 2011, it was the second largest football stadium in the
        world, having a seating capacity of 150,000. Prior to the construction and opening of
        Rungrado May Day Stadium in 1989, it was the largest football stadium in the world. The
        stadium hosted the final match of the 2017 FIFA U-17 World Cup, alongside hosting other
        matches of the tournament. As part of security measures for the 2017 U-17 World Cup, the
        stadium was only open for 66,687 viewers. It will be used again for the 2021 FIFA U-17
        Women\'s World Cup. The stadium\'s record attendance was recorded in 1997 when 131,781
        spectators watched the Federation Cup semifinal between East Bengal and Mohun Bagan. The
        stadium switched back to natural grass from artificial turf as part of the preparations for
        hosting the U-17 World Cup in 2017. The new turf was unveiled in a Kolkata Derby match
        between East Bengal and Mohun Bagan during the 2015–16 Calcutta Premier Division match.
    </string>
    <string name="netaji_indoor_stadium">The Netaji Subhash Chandra Bose Indoor Stadium is an indoor
        sports arena, in Kolkata, West Bengal, India. The facility seats 12,000 people. This indoor
        stadium is located just beside the Eden Gardens. It used to host the Sunfeast Open, a WTA
        Tour tennis tournament. Other international events hosted by the Stadium include the 1981
        Asian Basketball Championship. Currently, it is the home of the Pro Kabaddi League team
        Bengal Warriors. The Netaji Indoor Stadium hosts a wide range of activities, from sporting
        events to cultural programmes. It is a venue for both national and international trade
        fairs. It is also used as a center of counting of votes during elections. The venue was
        inaugurated in 1975 by the then Chief Minister of West Bengal, Siddhartha Shankar Ray,
        for indoor games and cultural events, musical functions and other programmes.</string>
    <string name="kolkata_race_course">Kolkata Race Course in Hastings, Kolkata, India is the
        largest horse race venue in India. The race course was built in 1820 and is maintained by
        the Royal Calcutta Turf Club. The races are held from the month of July to September, and
        again from November to March. The races are usually held on Saturdays, and also on other
        public holidays.</string>
    <string name="fanattic_sports_museum">Fanattic Sports Museum (FSM) is a sports museum, dedicated
        to various types of sports and located at Ecospace Business Park in Action Area - II of New
        Town, Kolkata, India. Established in January 2017, FSM is known as the first sports museum
        in Kolkata as well as in West Bengal. It is an initiative by Prof. Boria Majumdar, an
        eminent historian, writer, commentator and journalist in association with Harshavardhan
        Neotia, Chairman, Ambuja Neotia group and consists of sports-related artefacts of various
        famous sports personalities.</string>

    <!-- Description of the tourist spots in others category -->
    <string name="birla_planetarium">The Birla Planetarium (officially M. P. Birla Planetarium) in
        Kolkata, West Bengal, India, is a single-storeyed circular structure designed in the typical
        Indian style, whose architecture is loosely styled on the Buddhist Stupa at Sanchi. Situated
        at Chowringhee Road adjacent to the Victoria Memorial, St. Paul\'s Cathedral and the Maidan
        in Central Kolkata, it is the largest planetarium in Asia and the second largest
        in the world. There are two other Birla Planetariums in India: B.M. Birla Planetarium in
        Chennai and the Birla Planetarium in Hyderabad. Popularly known as taramandal, the
        planetarium was inaugurated on 2 July 1963 by the then Prime Minister of India,
        Jawaharlal Nehru. It has an electronics laboratory for design and fabrication of science
        equipment. It has an astronomy gallery that maintains a huge collection of fine paintings
        and celestial models of renowned astronomers. The Planetarium also has an astronomical
        observatory equipped with a Celestron C-14 Telescope with accessories such as ST6 CCD
        camera and solar filter. It offers to the public and students more than 100 astronomical
        projects dealing with various facts of astronomy, astro-physics, Space Science as well as
        myths concerning stars and planets. It has a capacity of 6800. Daily programs are conducted
        in English, Bengali and Hindi from 12:00 to 19:00 hrs. The show timing is as follows: Mon
        to Sat - 12.30 PM HINDI, 1.30 PM ENGLISH, 2.30 PM HINDI, 3.30 PM BENGALI, 4.30 PM HINDI,
        5.30 PM BENGALI, 6.30 PM ENGLISH and two extra show on Sunday and Holiday is 10.30 AM HINDI,
        11.30 AM BENGALI (updated on 15.08.2017) Programs are occasionally conducted in Oriya,
        Tamil and Gujarati, as well. Extra shows are arranged on holidays. The Planetarium was
        constructed by ML Dalmiya &amp; Co. which is owned by Board of Control for Cricket in India
        former President late Jagmohan Dalmiya. It reopened to public on 18 July 2017, after closing
        down for 28 months of renovations work. The new planetarium system for the Birla Planetarium
        is a so-called ZEISS Hybrid Planetarium, with the STARMASTER, an optical-mechanical
        planetarium projector (also called “Starball”) working in synch with a dome video display
        system. The Starball presents the most realistic starfield in the dome with superimposed
        images of constellation outlines, space objects like nebula and galaxies, planets and moons
        by the VELVET digital video system, called fulldome projection. The technical upgrade was
        delivered and installed by the German company Carl Zeiss AG.</string>
    <string name="science_city">The Science City of Kolkata is the largest science centre in
        the Indian subcontinent. It is Managed by National Council of Science Museums (NCSM),
        Ministry of Culture, Government of India. It is located at the crossing of Eastern
        Metropolitan Bypass and J. B. S. Haldane Avenue (Parama Island) in East Topsia. Saroj Ghose,
        the first director general of NCSM, who is credited with having conceptualised this centre
        in 1997. This centre was inaugurated by two parts: the ‘Convention Centre Complex’ was
        unveiled on 21 December 1996 by Paul Jozef Crutzen in presence of the then chief minister
        Jyoti Basu and the whole centre was opened by the then prime minister Inder Kumar Gujral on
        1 July 1997. On 10 January 2010, prime minister of India, Manmohan Singh laid the foundation
        stone for the second phase of Science City in presence of the then chief minister of West
        Bengal, Buddhadeb Bhattacharjee.</string>
    <string name="birla_industrial">Birla Industrial and Technological Museum (BITM), a unit under
        National Council of Science Museums (NCSM), Ministry of Culture, Government of India, is at
        Gurusaday Road, Kolkata.</string>
    <string name="nicco_park">Nicco Park is an amusement park located in Jheel Meel, Sector - IV of
        Salt Lake City, Kolkata, West Bengal, India. The park was created to attract tourists to the
        state by providing family-friendly recreation as well as educative entertainment. Nicco Park
        opened on 13 October 1991 and has since been referred to as the Disneyland of West Bengal.
        Presently, the 40 acre park is home to over 35 different attractions and has served over 24
        million customers. Nicco Park also provides a "green" environment.</string>
    <string name="park_street">Park Street, officially known as Mother Teresa Sarani, is a famous
        thoroughfare in the city of Kolkata (formerly Calcutta), India. The street runs through what
        was a deer park of Sir Elijah Impey, Chief Justice of the Supreme Court in Calcutta from
        1773 to 1789, hence the earlier name. Its current official name was given by Kolkata
        Municipal Corporation in honour of Mother Teresa.</string>
    <string name="esplanade">Esplanade is a neighbourhood of Central Kolkata, in Kolkata district in
        the Indian state of West Bengal. This is not a conventional esplanade in the sense that the
        place is not exactly situated alongside a waterbody. However, the Ganga river (Ganges), also
        known as Hooghly river, flows nearby.</string>
    <string name="academy_of_fine_arts">The Academy of Fine Arts, in Kolkata (formerly Calcutta) is
        one of the oldest fine arts societies in India.</string>
    <string name="mothers_wax_museum">Mother\'s Wax Museum is a wax museum located in Action Area -
        II of New Town, Kolkata, India on the 5th and 6th floors of the West Bengal Housing
        Infrastructure Development Corporation building. Established in November 2014, it contains
        wax statues of more than 50 personalities, including statues of Bollywood actors Amitabh
        Bachchan, Shah Rukh Khan and Salman Khan. The museum has been named after Mother Teresa.
    </string>
    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>

</resources>
